<module>
	<rawname>framework</rawname>
	<modtype>framework</modtype>
	<repo>standard</repo>
	<name>FreePBX Framework</name>
	<version>12.0.1beta6</version>
	<publisher>FreePBX</publisher>
	<license>GPLv2+</license>
	<licenselink>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt</licenselink>
	<candisable>no</candisable>
	<canuninstall>no</canuninstall>
	<changelog>
		*12.0.1beta6* FREEPBX-7517 log invalid logins to a security file for parsing
		*12.0.1beta5* Packaging fixes
		*12.0.1beta4* Change link on landing page from recordings to UCP
		*12.0.1beta3* Copy/replace fixes
		*12.0.1beta2* CLI, If repo doesnt exist check for it online
		*12.0.1beta1* First Beta Release
		*12.0.1alpha59* Silence a warning
		*12.0.1alpha58* Unmet depends are auto downloaded through CLI
		*12.0.1alpha57* Run trust key inside of install_amp, fix class loader
		*12.0.1alpha56* GPG Fixes
		*12.0.1alpha55* Turn on Asterisk Manager on module installs
		*12.0.1alpha54* Support for Module Namespaces
		*12.0.1alpha53* Prevent fatal on upgrade if textarea missing
		*12.0.1alpha52* Added new textarea type and other small fixes
		*12.0.1alpha51* Fix issue with gpg checks
		*12.0.1alpha50* FREEPBX-3481 fix login issue when using amportal
		*12.0.1alpha49* Preping for beta release, final alpha changes
		*12.0.1alpha48* Changes for Second Database class
		*12.0.1alpha47* Update jquery to a stable version and update font-awesome
		*12.0.1alpha46* Hide Framework signatures for now
		*12.0.1alpha45* Added Support for Module Signature Checking.
		*12.0.1alpha44* Add support for FreePBX::Modulename(), Return false if we couldnt run install or uninstall, Fixes for manager.conf errors, Use AMPDBHOST, don't hard code localhost.
		*12.0.1alpha43* Minor AJAX Changes to support non-standard ports.
		*12.0.1alpha42* FREEPBX-7344 FreePBX generated CSS link for module css files is wrong
		*12.0.1alpha41* Bring in Less/CSS updates and minor BMO additions.
		*12.0.1alpha40* Bring in all development work, including css to less work
		*12.0.1alpha38* Only define DB classes one time
		*12.0.1alpha37* Update framework DB to have helper functions for functions that mysqli needs
		*12.0.1alpha36* Revert Use mysqli extension for database access, if available.
		*12.0.1alpha35* #7141 Use mysqli extension for database access, if available.
		*12.0.1alpha34* Remove need for jqueryUI buttonset on browsers with CSS3 native support
		*12.0.1alpha33* Change security shield functionality, add advanced setting to disable nightly update checking
		*12.0.1alpha32* Add Japanese language support
		*12.0.1alpha31* FREEPBX-7119
		*12.0.1alpha30* #7168 and CSS Updates
		*12.0.1alpha29* Enable Less Support
		*12.0.1alpha28* Ensure module hooks aren't duplicated.
		*12.0.1alpha26* Move BMO Startup to enable proper module integration
		*12.0.1alpha25* BMO issues with Commercial Modules
		*12.0.1alpha24* Minor BMO cleanups
		*12.0.1alpha22* #7123 SECURITY ISSUE introduced in 2.9
		*12.0.1alpha18* #6471 Allow better voicemail passwords
		*12.0.1alpha17* Set CustomPresence on dynamic hints, when available.
		*12.0.1alpha16* Added help text bubbles to feature code admin re FREEPBX-6903
		*12.0.1alpha15* Add remote-unlock feature. This is disabled by default.
		*12.0.1alpha14* Remove unneeded warning when processing commercial modules.
		*12.0.1alpha13* Automatically enable repos from module_admin if used with --repo also make standard, standard
		*12.0.1alpha12* Full fix for module_admin functionality to always attempt to look at master modulexml for list of repos
		*12.0.1alpha11* BMO didn't know how to preload a module.
		*12.0.1alpha10* Update to 10, numerous fixes here and there
		*12.0.1alpha9* And then there was 9, set the Version of FreePBX correctly
		*12.0.1alpha8* BMO fixes and other things that make this awesome
		*12.0.1alpha7* Prep for public release 1
		*12.0.1alpha6* Update Global SIP Settings Driver Selection
		*12.0.1alpha5* More Module Admin tweaks and fixes
		*12.0.1alpha4* Module Admin Javascript bugs fixed
		*12.0.1alpha3* Module Admin working. Might have some bugs.
		*12.0.1alpha2* Good start to the first alpha, forgot to package the new javascripts
	</changelog>
	<description>
		This module provides a facility to install bug fixes to the framework code that is not otherwise housed in a module
	</description>
	<depends>
		<phpversion>5.3.0</phpversion>
	</depends>
	<supported>
		<version>12.0</version>
	</supported>
	<category>Admin</category>
  <location>packages/framework/framework-12.0.1alpha40.tgz</location>
  <md5sum>75b495796505ba06ccf0aaf2156d9bbc</md5sum>
  <sha1>a4aacfc5b9c257a0de8ecf72e94f8c7f658508da</sha1>
</module>
